Guide to the G. Ridgley Loux papers, 1974-1993
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 3: Plans, 1981-1993; (7 boxes)
  - Area III Annual Plan Review, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    347.8
  - Bowman Green Rezoning and Jonathan's Keep Site Plan, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    352.6
  - Countywide Annual Plan Review, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    347.12
  - Fairfax County Master Plan, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    348.6
  - Springwood-Phase 2, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    411.8
  - Boston Properties (booklet), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    348.10
  - API Record File, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    348.9a
  - API Record File, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    348.9b
  - Fairfax Center Area Plan Amendment Nominations, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    351.2
  - Review of Fairfax Center Plan Amendments, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    351.3
  - Annual Plan Review-Area III Items, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    350.2
  - Annual Plan Reviews-Area II Items, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    350.1
  - Annual Plan Review (APR), 1985 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    350.3
  - Annual Plan Review-County Wide Items, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    349.5
  - Land Use, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    413.7
  - Hunter Mill Office Plan, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    349.4a
  - Hunter Mill Office Plan, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    349.4b
  - Parkridge-Phase II, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    411.10
  - House Bill 1033-Construction Bonds, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    411.9
  - Reston INdustrial Planned Community, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    354.4
  - Adopted Amendments to the Fairfax County Plan, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    354.2
  - Countrywide Annual Plan Review, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Area III Items, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    354.3
  - Reston Industrial Planned Community File, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    354.6
  - Reston Industrial Planned Community File, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    354.5
  - Town Center Rezoning, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    352.3
  - Traffic (Bypass), 1986 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    352.5
  - Town Center, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    358.3a
  - Town Center, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    358.3b
  - Plan Change, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    355.2
  - Plan Change, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    355.1
  - Town Center Rezonings, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    356.6
  - Town Center Rezonings, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    356.7
  - Zoning Ordinance Amendments, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    411.11
  - Public Transportation and Land Use Relationship-Joe Stowers' notes, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    357.3
  - Board Call Up of I District Site Plans, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    356.8
  - Bowman Tract, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    359.9
  - St. John Neumann Parish, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    356.5
  - Miller Office Building-1801 Reston Parkway, Reston, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    360.6
  - Policy Review-Proposed Amendments to the Comprehensive Plan, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    359.1
  - County Government Center Fairfax Center, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    357.8
  - Redevelopment, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    412.2
  - Reston's Children's Center, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    359.2
    - Meeting Summary with Residents of Tanner's Cluster with Accompanying Letter, August 8, 1988; 1.
    - Reston Children's Center Diagrams with Accompanying Letter and Memo, 9 September 1988; 10.
  - Work Program to Revise the Policy Element of the Comprehensive Plan, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    359.5
  - Policy Review Year-Annual Plan Review, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    358.7
  - McDonald's and Taco Bell, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    357.9
  - Centennial Commerce Executive Park, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    357.10
  - Transportation-Reston Hunter Mill Road, Park and Ride Lot, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    361.6
  - Fairfax Planning Horizons/Citizens Guide to Update Process, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    361.2
  - Bowman Tract, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    359.8
  - Sheraton, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    412.6
  - Sheraton, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    412.7
  - Ten Year Transportation Funding and Construction Plan, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    363.3
  - Reston Inn and Conference Center Venture-Zoning, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    362.6
  - Town Center, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    358.4
  - Planning and Rezoning Commission (PRC) Task Force, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    364.2
  - Hechingers/Bradlee Center, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    413.4
  - Plaza America, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    413.5
  - Planning and Rezoning Commission District Task Force-Summary of Major Recommendations, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    413.6
  - Development of School Sites-Reston, 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    353.5
  - Town Center Rezoning, 1980-1986 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    352.4
  - Parkridge File, 1982-1988 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    411.13
  - Parkridge File, 1982-1988 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    411.12
  - GE Site-Rezoning to I-5, 1983-1989 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    411.17
  - Redevelopment, 1985-1988 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    412.1
  - Redevelopment, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    412.3
- Series 4: General Information, 1974-1993; (5.5 boxes)
  The papers cover a variety of topics dealing with building projects in Reston, such as Town Center and others. Also among the paperwork are brochures and information on the developments.
  - Reading File, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    347.6
  - Reading File, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    347.7
  - Reston Community Association: Bylaws Articles of Incorporation, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    411.3
  - Datatronix, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    355.11
  - Community, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    348.1
  - Traffic-Dulles Lanes, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    355.10
  - Lake Anne, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    347.11
  - Lake Anne, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    347.10
  - Equipment (Defective, Incompatible, Unreliable), 1983 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    356.4
  - Reston Community Association-Mailing LIst, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    411.5
  - Newsclippings, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    411.18
  - Meeting at MVP Sunrise Valley Dr. Development, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    347.13
  - Polo Club-Reston, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    348.4
  - Soapstone Convenience Center-Reston, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    348.5
  - Signs and Laws Relating Thereto, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Helicopter, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    348.7
  - Lake Fairfax Business Center, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    411.7
  - Memos, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    353.2
  - Memos, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    353.3
  - Dollar Values-Miscellaneous Parcels, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    353.6
  - Centennial Development Corporation, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    349.3
  - Commercial and Residential Alliance at Glade and Sunrise (CRAGS), 1985 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    351.4
  - Reston-20th Anniversary Symposium, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    351.7
  - Reston-"Fringe" Development, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    351.6
  - Rando-Air-Rights Town Center, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    351.5
  - Town Center-May 21, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    351.9
  - Town Center-May 21, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    351.8a
  - Town Center-May 21, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    351.8b
  - Hospital-Humana, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    349.1
    - "Humana Group in New Fight" (From The Connection), March 17, 1982; 19.
    - A Hospital Close To Home (Petition for support of hospital), December 1981; 22.
  - Land Use-Zoning Developments Articles, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    348.2
  - Daybridge, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    353.7
  - Freddie Mac, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    353.8
  - Reston Farm Market, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    355.5
  - Drunk Driving, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    353.9
  - Reston-General, Articles, Brochures, etc., 1986 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    358.1a
  - Reston-General, Articles, Brochures, etc., 1986 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    358.1b
  - District Revision, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    354.7a
  - District Revision, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    354.7b
  - William L. Berry and Company, Incorporated, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    411.2
  - Dart-Light Rail, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    354.9
  - Fairfax Newsletter, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    364.5
  - Scape, Reston, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    357.4
  - Miscellaneous (Agenda), 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    360.2
  - Miscellaneous (Agenda), 1988 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    360.1
  - Sunrise Valley Drive, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    411.15
  - Reston Governance Options, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    411.16
  - Fairfax Newsletter, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    364.6a
  - Fairfax Newsletter, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    364.6b
  - Town Center, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    358.2a
  - Town Center, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    358.2b
  - Town Center, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    361.5
  - Miscellaneous (Agenda), 1989 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    360.3
  - Fairfax Newsletter, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    364.7a
  - Fairfax Newsletter, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    364.7b
  - Fairfax Newsletter, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    365.1a
  - Fairfax Newsletter, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    365.1b
  - Community Database Content, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    412.8
  - Hunter Mill Road Project, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    412.9
  - Reston Neighborhoods, 1990s (Box 23, Folder 8)
    411.1
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Sunset Corporate Plaza, Two Brochures, 1990s (Box 23, Folder 9)
    364.4
  - Fairfax Newsletter, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    365.2
  - Hunter Mill Corridor News, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    364.3
  - Prison Fellowship, 1983-1985 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    349.2
  - Miller Office Building-1801 Reston Parkway, Reston, 1986-1989 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    360.5
  - Tyson II Development, 1960-1989 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    359.6
  - Urbanization of the Suburbs, 1985-1987 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    356.2
  - Miscellaneous, 1984-1990 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    412.5
  - Power Outages, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    411.6
  - Glut in Office Space-Washington Metropolitan Area, 1983-1988 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    357.5
  - Planning and Zoning, 1982-1986 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    353.1